Danny Kaye and Sylvia Fine Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Scripts, 1944-1986 (Box-folder 443-482)
  - The Danny Kaye Show, 1963-1967
    - Episode #119, 1967, March 8, 95519945 (Box-folder 469/2)
    - Episode #120, 1967, April 5, 95520054 (Box-folder 469/3)
    - Episode #121, 1967, March 15, 95520063 (Box-folder 469/4)
    - Episode #122, 1967, March 29, 95520157 (Box-folder 469/5)
    - Episode #123, 1967, March 22, 95520282 (Box-folder 470/1)
    - Episode #124, 1967, April 12, 95520319 (Box-folder 470/2)
  - The John Gary Show, 1966
    Arranged numerically by episode number.
    - Episode #1 - Episode #5 (Box-folder 471/1-5)
    - Episode #6 - Episode #9 (Box-folder 472/1-4)
    - Episode #10 - Episode #12 (Box-folder 473/1-3)
  - Films, 1944-1968
    Film scripts for all Kaye films except A Song is Born; many are housed in their original embossed leather binders and include production stills. Additional production stills are found in the Photographs series.
    Arranged alphabetically by title. LCCNs provide links to the full catalog record for each title.
    - The Court Jester, November 15, 1954, Leather bound; contains 16 black and white production stills; Revised final version.; 95501393 (Box-folder 474/1)
    - The Five Pennies, October 3, 1958, Leather bound; contains 47 black and white production stills; Revised "White" version.; 95500866 (Box-folder 474/2)
    - Hans Christian Andersen, December 20, 1951, Leather bound; personalized; contains 35 black and white production stills; Final version.; 95502663 (Box-folder 474/3)
    - Happy Times, August 7, 1958, Leather bound; contains 6 production stills; Released title: The Inspector General; 95501456 (Box-folder 475/1)
    - Intermission, 1954-1957, Released title: The Five Pennies (Box-folder 475/2)
    - The Kid from Brooklyn, June 1, 1945, Leather bound; contains 12 black and white production stills; Final version.; 95502584 (Box-folder 475/3)
    - Knock on Wood, May 19, 1953, Leather bound; contains 44 black and white production stills; Final "White" version.; 95500322 (Box-folder 475/4)
    - The Madwoman of Chaillot, February 21, 1968 (Box-folder 476/1-2)
    - The Man from the Diner's Club, May 31, 1962, Leather bound; contains 50 black and white production stills; Final version. (Box-folder 476/3)
    - Me and the Colonel, October 7, 1957, Leather bound; contains 28 black and white production stills; Revised final draft.; 95500418 (Box-folder 476/4)
    - Merry Andrew, July 1, 1957, Leather bound; contains 40 black and white production stills; 95502078 (Box-folder 477/1)
    - On the Double, November 1960, Leather bound; contains 46 black and white production stills; 95500808 (Box-folder 477/2)
    - On the Riviera, September 13, 1950, Leather bound; contains 53 black and white production stills; Final shooting version.; 95502201 (Box-folder 477/3)
    - The Secret Life of Walter Mitty, 1946, Leather bound; contains 31 black and white production stills; 95501130 (Box-folder 478/1)
    - Up in Arms, June 1943, Leather bound; copy 1 contains 4 photographs, copy 2, personalized, contains 18 photographs; Revised, final version.; 95502401 (Box-folder 478/2-3)
    - White Christmas, September 14, 1953, Leather bound; contains 32 black and white production stills; 2nd revision, final version.; 95501266 (Box-folder 479/1)
    - Wonder Man, 1944-1945, Leather bound; contains 20 black and white production stills; 95502507 (Box-folder 479/2)
  - Television Appearances, 1961-1986
    Scripts for various stand-alone television programs in which Danny Kaye appeared.
    Arranged alphabetically by program title.
    - Cock-a-doodle-doo!, 1961 (Box-folder 480/1)
    - The Cosby Show, #0216-16: "The Dentist," 1986, 90713426 (Box-folder 480/2)
    - Danny Kaye's "Look-In" at the Met, 1975, 96506170 (Box-folder 480/3-4)
    - The Enchanted World of Danny Kaye, 1971, 96519232 (Box-folder 180/5)
    - Epcot Center Opening Celebration, 1982 (Box-folder 480/6)
    - An Evening with John Denver, 1975 (Box-folder 480/7)
    - Here Comes Peter Cottontail, 1971, 89706471 (Box-folder 480/8)
    - Peter Pan, 1975 (Box-folder 481/1)
    - Pinocchio, February 18, 1976 (Box-folder 481/2-3)
    - Ringling Brothers Barnum and Bailey Circus, January 1979 (Box-folder 481/4)
    - Defend to the Death, September 15, 1980, Released title: Skokie (Box-folder 481/5)
    - Skokie, October 18, 1980, 95521508 (Box-folder 481/6-7)
    - The Twilight Zone: "Paladin of the Lost Hour," 1985, 91727048 (Box-folder 482/1)
  - Theatrical Productions, 1954, 1970
    - The Flowering Plum, 1954 (Box-folder 482/2)
    - Two by Two, Revisions, 1970 (Box-folder 482/3)
- Correspondence, 1940s-1991 (Box 483-500, 624, 791)
  Typed and handwritten letters, greeting cards, and telegrams to Danny Kaye and/or Sylvia Fine. Enclosures include photographs, clippings, and other items. Birthday, Christmas, condolence, and get-well messages comprise the bulk of this material. Congratulatory notes found here supplement those interspersed throughout the collection.
  Arranged alphabetically by surname of sender or topic.
  - Albert Hall performance, 1966 (Box-folder 483/1)
  - Allen, Steve, 1986, 1988 (Box-folder 483/2)
  - Astor, Brooke, 1986 (Box-folder 483/3)
  - "A" Miscellaneous, 1959-1988, Correspondents include Julian "Cannonball" Adderly, Rupert Allan, and Anna Bing Arnold. (Box-folder 483/4)
  - Ben Franklin School, 1975 (Box-folder 483/5)
  - Benny, Jack, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 483/6)
  - Birthday Greetings - Kaye, Danny, 1957 (Box-folder 791/2/)
  - Birthday Greetings – Kaye, Danny, 1964, 1966-1968, Correspondents include Sylvia Fine, Holly Hitzing, Johnny Kan, Victoria Meyerink, Carroll Richter, and Mary Roebling. (Box-folder 483/7)
  - Birthday Greetings – Kaye, Danny, 1969, 1970, Correspondents include Sylvia Fine, Johnny Green, Victoria Meyerink, Wayne Newton, and Mary Roebling. (Box-folder 483/8)
  - Birthday Greetings – Kaye, Danny, 1972, 1974, Correspondents include Sylvia Fine, Holly Hitzing, Johnny Green, and Mary Roebling. (Box-folder 483/9)
  - Birthday Greetings – Kaye, Danny, 1977, Correspondents include Johnny Green, Irv Kupcinet, and Paige Rence. (Box-folder 483/10)
  - Birthday Greetings – Kaye, Danny, 1978 (Box-folder 483/11)
  - Birthday Greetings – Kaye, Danny, 1982, Correspondents include Sylvia Fine, Dena Kaye, James Levine, Stavros Niachos, Mary Roebling, and Harold I. Silverman. (Box-folder 483/12)
  - Birthday Greetings – Kaye, Danny, 1983, Correspondents include Roberto Goizueta, Holly Hitzing, Dena Kaye, Teddy Kollek, Queen Beatrix of Holland, Anton Mosiman, and Mary Roebling. (Box-folder 483/13)
  - Birthday Greetings – Kaye, Danny, 1984, Correspondents include Olive Behrendt, Sylvia Fine, Roberto Goizueta, Vi Marriott, Roddy McDowall, Anton Mosiman, the Muppets, Ronald Reagan, and Harold I. Silverman. (Box-folder 483/14)
  - Birthday Greetings – Kaye, Danny, 1985, Correspondents include Holly Hitzing, Roddy McDowall, Anton Moseman, Peter and Annette O'Malley, and Carroll Richter. (Box-folder 484/1)
  - Birthday Greetings – Kaye, Danny, 1986, Correspondents include Holly Hitzing, Anton Mosiman, and Peter and Annette O'Malley. (Box-folder 484/2)
  - Birthday Greetings – Kaye, Danny, 1987, Correspondents include Holly Hitzing, Harvey Korman, the Muppets, Harold I. Silverman, and Catarina Valenti. (Box-folder 484/3)
  - Birthday Greetings – Kaye, Danny, undated, 1985, undated; Correspondents include Sylvia Fine. (Box-folder 484/4)
  - Birthday Greetings – Fine, Sylvia, 1972 (Box-folder 484/5)
  - Birthday Greetings – Fine, Sylvia, 1973, Correspondents include Dore Schary and Jolene Schlatter. (Box-folder 484/6)
  - Birthday Greetings – Fine, Sylvia, 1976, Correspondents include Mary Roebling. (Box-folder 484/7)
  - Birthday Greetings – Fine, Sylvia, 1977 (Box-folder 484/8)
  - Birthday Greetings – Fine, Sylvia, 1978, Correspondents include Olive Behrendt, Dena Kaye, Roddy McDowall, Carroll Richter, Dore Schary, and Nancy Walker. (Box-folder 484/9)
  - Birthday Greetings – Fine, Sylvia, 1980, Correspondents include Carol Burnett, Robert A. Forrest, Cynthia Lindsey, Roddy McDowall, Carroll Richter, and Jolene Schlatter. (Box-folder 484/10)
  - Birthday Greetings – Fine, Sylvia, 1981, Correspondents include Rupert Allan, Olive Behrendt, Frank McCarthy, Roddy McDowall, Carl Reiner, Nancy Walker, and Margaret Tallichet Wyler.; Includes photographs of Danny Kaye, Sylvia Fine, and Jack Lemmon. (Box-folder 485/1)
  - Birthday Greetings – Fine, Sylvia, 1982, Correspondents include Steve Allen, Dom DeLuise, Jack Lemmon, Frank McCarthy, and Jayne Meadows. (Box-folder 485/2)
  - Birthday Greetings – Fine, Sylvia, 1983, Correspondents include Anne Douglas, Dena Kaye, and Dinah Shore.; Includes photographs. (Box-folder 485/3)
  - Birthday Greetings – Fine, Sylvia, 1984 (Box-folder 485/4)
  - Birthday Greetings – Fine, Sylvia, 1985, Correspondents include Anne Douglas, Dena Kaye, and Roddy McDowall.; Includes photographs of Danny Kaye and Sylvia Fine. (Box-folder 485/5)
  - Birthday Greetings – Fine, Sylvia, 1986, Correspondents include Rupert Allan, Anne Douglas, Christopher Hart, Dena Kaye, James Levine, Peter and Annette O'Malley, and Jolene Schlatter. (Box-folder 486/1)
  - Birthday Greetings – Fine, Sylvia, 1987, Correspondents include Kitty Carlisle Hart, Dena Kaye, and Carroll Richter. (Box-folder 486/2)
  - Birthday Greetings – Fine, Sylvia, 1988, Correspondents include Michael Dukakis, Dena Kaye, Pauline Trigère, and Jane Withers. (Box-folder 486/3)
  - British Royal Family, 1948-1989, Correspondents include Princess Alexandra; Queen Elizabeth II; Elizabeth, Queen Mother; George VI, Princess Margaret; Princess Marina; Philip, Duke of Edinburgh. (Box-folder 486/4)
  - Brown, Helen Gurley and David, 1973-1982, 1987 (Box-folder 486/5)
  - Burns, George, 1957 (Box-folder 486/6)
  - Bush, George, 1987 (Box-folder 486/7)
  - "Ba-Bl" Miscellaneous, 1947-1949, 1957-1988, Correspondents include Herbert Baker, Buzzie Bavasi, Olive Behrendt, and Harry Beller.; Includes letter to Edgar F. Magnin handwritten by Danny Kaye. (Box-folder 486/8)
  - "Bo-By" Miscellaneous, 1948, 1958-1988, undated, Correspondents include Ann Brinkley, Susan Brinkley, Ella Brennan, Dick Brennan, Jerry Bock, John Brademus, Tom Bradley, Cubby Broccoli, Charles R. Bronfman, Gaby Bruyere, Richard J. Byrd, and Sonny Burke. (Box-folder 486/9)
  - Campion, Clifford, 1980-1988 (Box-folder 486/10)
  - Cantor, Eddie, 1952 (Box-folder 486/11)
  - Cerf, Bennett and Phyllis, 1950-1953 (Box-folder 486/12)
  - Chevalier, Maurice, 1959, 1967, undated (Box-folder 486/13)
  - Christmas Greetings, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 487/1)
  - Christmas Greetings, 1956-1957, undated; Correspondents include Bob Hope. (Box-folder 791/3/)
  - Christmas Thank Yous, 1963 (Box-folder 487/2)
  - Christmas Greetings, 1964 (Box-folder 487/3)
  - Christmas Greetings, 1965, Correspondents include Eugene Ormandy, Bill Paley, and Otto Preminger. (Box-folder 487/4)
  - Christmas Greetings, 1966, Correspondents include Margot Fonteyn, Ira and Lee Gershwin, Katherine Graham, William Lear, Otto Preminger, and David Sarnoff. (Box-folder 487/5)
  - Christmas Greetings, 1967, Correspondents include Buzzie Bavasi, Phyllis Cerf, Maurice Chevalier, Margot Fonteyn, Katherine Graham, Hubert Humphrey, Jacob Javits, Johnny Kan, Mary Lasker, Abe Lastvogel, Mary Lindsey, Henry Cabot Lodge, Barbara and Bill Paley, Otto Preminger, Max Rabb, David Sarnoff, Jerry Silverman, and Stuart Symington. (Box-folder 487/6)
  - Christmas Greetings, 1968, Correspondents include Federico Fellini, Kitty Carlisle Hart, Mary Lasker, Katherine Graham, Anna Rosenberg Hoffman, Nicholas Katzenbach, Victoria Meyerink, Otto Preminger, Joan Rivers, David Sarnoff, Barbara Windom. (Box-folder 487/7)
  - Christmas Greetings, 1969, Correspondents include Mary Lasker, Gregory Peck, Otto Preminger, and Irene Selznick. (Box-folder 487/8)
  - Christmas Greetings, 1971, Correspondents include Theo Bikel, Katherine Graham, Mary Lindsey, and Jerry Silverman. (Box-folder 487/9)
  - Christmas Greetings, 1972, Correspondents include Anna Rosenberg Hoffman, Dena Kaye, and Veronique Peck. (Box-folder 487/10)
  - Christmas Greetings, 1973, Correspondents include Jacob Javits, Frank McCarthy, and Roddy McDowall. (Box-folder 487/11)
  - Christmas Greetings, 1974, Correspondents include Buzzie Bavasi, Michael deBakey, Harry Ellis Dickson, Anne Douglas, Anna Rosenberg Hoffman, Jacob Javits, Mary Lasker, John Lindsey, Frank McCarthy, Annette and Peter O'Malley, Alan Pakula, Nelson Rockefeller, Willie Mae Rogers, Jerry Silverman, and Natalie Wood. (Box-folder 487/12)
  - Christmas Greetings, 1975, Correspondents include Katrina deBakey, Bob Hope, Dena Kaye, Bill Lear, and Victoria Meyerink. (Box-folder 488/1)
  - Christmas Greetings, 1976, Correspondents include Rupert Allan, Jules Bass, Buzzie Bavasi, Anne Douglas, Douglas Fairbanks, Jr., Johnny Green, Kitty Carlisle Hart, Jay Heifetz, Anna Rosenberg Hoffman, Jacob Javits, Ed Kennebeck, Henry Kissinger, Mary Lasker, John Lindsey, Roddy McDowall, Daniel Melnick, Jackie Onassis, Casey Ribiciff, Carroll Richter, Jan Tillisch, Natalie Wood, and Ardeshir Zahedi. (Box-folder 488/2)
  - Christmas Greetings, 1977, Correspondents include Katrin deBakey, Buff Chandler, Sylvia Fine, Katharine Graham, Cathy Hart, Anna Rosenberg Hoffman, Dena Kaye, Ed Kennebeck, Mary Lasker, Victoria Meyerink, Jackie Onassis, Jerry Robbins, Jerry Silverman, Beverly Sills, Natalie Wood, and Ardeshir Zahedi. (Box-folder 488/3)
  - Christmas Greetings, 1978, Correspondents include Buzzie Bavasi, Ellin and Irving Berlin, Carol Burnett, Vikki Carr, Buff Chandler, Johnny Green, Cathy Hart, Anna Rosenberg Hoffman, Rock Hudson, Ed Kennebeck, Nancy Kissinger, Mary Lasker, Julius Lefkowitz, Sol Linowitz, Betty Mauceri, Victoria Meyerink, Roddy McDowall, Carroll Richter, and Natalie Wood. (Box-folder 488/4)
  - Christmas Greetings, 1979, Correspondents include Katrin deBakey, Sandy Duncan, Douglas Fairbanks, Jr., Cathy Hart, Kitty Carlisle Hart, Anna Rosenberg Hoffman, Ed Kennebeck, Mary Lasker, Mary Lindsey, Jack Lemmon, Sol Linowitz, Roddy McDowall, Zubin Mehta, the Muppets, Carroll Richter, and Beverly Sills. (Box-folder 488/5)
  - Christmas Greetings, 1980, Correspondents include Anna Bing Arnold, Larry Auerbach, Bob Balaban, Marie Briehl, Hernando Courtright, Sylvia Fine, Ira and Lee Gershwin, Johnny Green, Anna Rosenberg Hoffman, Dena Kaye, Ed Kennebeck, Burton Lane, Mary Lasker, Annette O'Malley, Carroll Richter, Jolene Schlatter, Beverly Sills, Robert Wagner, and Natalie Wood. (Box-folder 489/1)
  - Christmas Greetings, 1981, Correspondents include Hernando Courtright, Ira and Lee Gershwin, Cathy Hart, Ed Kennebeck, Peter O'Malley, Carroll Richter, Harold I. Silverman, Leonard Spigelgass, and Nancy Walker. (Box-folder 489/2)
  - Christmas Greetings, 1982, Correspondents include Larry Auerbach, James Beard, Helen Gurley Brown, Hugh Carey, Dom DeLuise, Anne Douglas, Ira Gershwin, Holly Hitzing, Anne Rosenberg Hoffman, Jacob Javits, Romaire Johnston, Danny Kaye, Dena Kaye, Ed Kennebeck, Henry Kissinger, Belton Kleberg, Burton Lane, Peter O'Malley, Itzhak Perlman, Rosemarie Sena, and Eugenia Zuckerman. (Box-folder 489/3)
  - Christmas Greetings, 1983, Correspondents include Josette Banzet, Dom DeLuise, Jane Fonda, Robert Goulet, Monty Hall, Kitty Carlisle Hart, Mary Hart, Marcella Hazan, Holly Hitzing, Stavros Niachros, Vin Scully, Beverly Sills, Isaac Stern, and Eugenia Zuckerman. (Box-folder 489/4)
  - Christmas Greetings, 1984, Correspondents include Chloe Aaron, Michael deBakey, Anne Douglas, Frank McCarthy, the Muppets, Annette O'Malley, Itzhak Perlman, Carroll Richter, Jolene Schlatter, and Eugenia Zuckerman. (Box-folder 489/5)
  - Christmas Greetings, 1985, Correspondents include Rupert Allan, H. G. Brown, Arlene Dahl, Michael deBakey, Anne Douglas, Cathy Hart, Kitty Carlisle Hart, Aly Khan, Dena Kaye, Jack Lemmon, Frank McCarthy, Roddy McDowall, Peter O'Malley, Ronald Reagan, Carroll Richter, Mary Roebling, Vin Scully Yves St. Laurent, Elizabeth Taylor, Gloria Vanderbilt, and Benay Venuta. (Box-folder 489/6)
  - Christmas Greetings, 1986, Correspondents include Mikhail Baryshnikov, Marie Briehl, Susan Brinkley, Arlene Dahl, Michael deBakey, John Denver, Anne and Kirk Douglas, Douglas Fairbanks, Jr., Cathy Hart, Christopher Hart, Dena Kaye, Mary Lasker, Jack Lemmon, Roddy McDowall, Rod McKuen, Annette O'Malley, Laurence Olivier, Itzhak Perlman, Prince Rainier, Princess Margriet, Elizabeth Taylor, and Paulene Trigère. (Box-folder 490/1)
  - Christmas Greetings, 1987, Correspondents include Arlene Dahl, Margot Fonteyn, Cathy Hart, Holly Hitzing, Dena Kaye, Mary Lasker, James Levine, Dorothy Rodgers, and Robert Wagner and Jill St. John. (Box-folder 490/2)
  - Christmas Greetings, 1988, Correspondents include Arlene Dahl, Agnes de Mille, Katherine Graham, Cathy Hart, Dena Kaye, Mary Lasker, Jack Lemmon, James Levine, Roddy McDowall, Zubin Mehta, the Muppets, Annette and Peter O'Malley, Dorothy Rodgers, and Robert Wagner. (Box-folder 490/3)
  - Christmas Greetings, undated, Correspondents include Maurice Chevalier, George Cukor, José Ferrar/Rosemary Clooney family, Margot Fonteyn, Judy Garland/Sid Luft family, Martyn Green, Bob Hope family, Greta Lauder, Sophie Tucker, and Prince Aly Khan.; Includes moving card with Danny Kaye as Santa Claus (Box-folder 490/4)
  - Claiborne, Craig, 1981 (Box-folder 490/5)
  - Clooney, Rosemary, 1967 (Box-folder 490/6)
  - Colbert, Claudette, undated (Box-folder 490/7)
  - Collart, Yanou, 1982, undated (Box-folder 490/8)
  - Collingwood, Charles, 1966 (Box-folder 490/9)
  - Condolences – Death of Danny Kaye, "A" 1987, Correspondents include Chloe Aaron, Alan Alda, Princess Alexandra, Steve Allen, Fred Astaire, Larry Auerbach, Margot Fonteyn, and Barbara Walters. (Box-folder 490/10)
  - Condolences – Death of Danny Kaye, "B" 1987, Correspondents include Lauren Bacall, Polly Bergen, Leonard Bernstein, Daniel J. Boorstein, Leslie Bricusse, Ann Brinkley, Susan Brinkley, Earl Brown, and Carol Burnett. (Box-folder 490/11)
  - Condolences – Death of Danny Kaye, "C" 1987, Correspondents include Clifford Campion, Hõrst Cerni, Van Cliburn, Claudette Colbert, David Craig, and Richard Crenna. (Box-folder 491/1)
  - Condolences – Death of Danny Kaye, "D" 1987, Correspondents include Jacques D'Amboise, Altovise Davis, Yãel Dayan, Fred De Cordova, Michael deBakey, John Denver, Placido Domingo, Kirk Douglas, the Dunhills, and Dominick Dunne. (Box-folder 491/2)
  - Condolences – Death of Danny Kaye, "E" 1987, Correspondents include Abba Eban and Queen Elizabeth II. (Box-folder 491/3)
  - Condolences – Death of Danny Kaye, "F" 1987, Correspondents include Jane Fonda, Shirlee Fonda, and Betty Furness. (Box-folder 491/4)
  - Condolences – Death of Danny Kaye, "G" 1987, Correspondents include King Carl Gustaf of Sweden, Eva Gabor, Zsa Zsa Gabor, Larry Gelbart, Lee Gershwin, June Golden, Barbara Grant, Johnny Green, Joel Grey, and Suzanne Pleshette. (Box-folder 491/5)
  - Condolences – Death of Danny Kaye, "H" 1987, Correspondents include Monty Hall, William Hammerstein, Pamela Harriman, Chaim Hertzog, Holly Hitzing, Bob and Dolores Hope, Ross Hunter, and Betty Hutton. (Box-folder 491/6)
  - Condolences – Death of Danny Kaye, "I-J" 1987, Correspondents include Van Johnson. (Box-folder 491/7)
  - Condolences – Death of Danny Kaye, "K" 1987, Correspondents include Garson Kanin, Dong Kingman, Henry and Nancy Kissinger, Leo Kolber, Teddy Kollek, and Irv Kupcinet. (Box-folder 491/8)
  - Condolences – Death of Danny Kaye, "L" 1987, Correspondents include Perry Lafferty, Schlomo Lahat, Burton Lane, Mary Lasker, Steve Lawrence and Eydie Gorme, Mary Lazar, Norman Lear, Eppie Lederer, Jack Lemmon, Lester S. Levy, John V. Lindsey, Sol Linowitz, Nedda and Josh Logan, and Queen Beatrix and Prince Claus. (Box-folder 491/9)
  - Condolences – Death of Danny Kaye, "M" 1987, Correspondents include Vi Marriott, Walter Matthau, Victor Mature, Paul Mazursky, Shirley McLaine, Mehli Mehta, Nancy and Zubin Mehta, Robert Merrill, Stanley Meyer, Liza Minnelli, and Anton Moseman. (Box-folder 491/10)
  - Condolences – Death of Danny Kaye, "N" 1987, Correspondents include Stavros Niachros. (Box-folder 492/1)
  - Condolences – Death of Danny Kaye, "O" 1987, Correspondents include Peter O'Malley and Laurence Olivier. (Box-folder 492/2)
  - Condolences – Death of Danny Kaye, "P-Q" 1987, Correspondents include Agnes de Mille, Norman Panama, Joseph Papp, Luciano Pavarotti, Veronique and Gregory Peck, Shimon Peres, Jacques Pepin, Itzhak Perlman, Bernadette Peters, Roberta Peters, and Hal Prince. (Box-folder 492/3)
  - Condolences – Death of Danny Kaye, "R" 1987, Correspondents include Josette Bauzet, Max Rabb, Yitzhak Rabin, Tony Randall, Ronald Reagan, Lynn Redgrave, Rex Reed, Carl Reiner, Abraham Ribicoff, Jerome Robbins, Flora Roberts, Dorothy Rodgers, Mary Roebling, and Barbara Rush. (Box-folder 492/4)
  - Condolences – Death of Danny Kaye, "S" 1987, Correspondents include Anna Moffo Sarnoff, George Schlatter, Arthur Schlesinger, Jr., Robert Schuller, Vin Scully, Daniel Meyer Selznick, Irene Selznick, Eric Sevareid, Donna Shalala, Run Run Shaw, Dinah Shore, Frank Sinatra, Oliver Smith, George Stevens, Jr., and Roger L. Stevens. (Box-folder 492/5)
  - Condolences – Death of Danny Kaye, "T" 1987, Correspondents include Topol and Pauline Trigère. (Box-folder 492/6)
  - Condolences – Death of Danny Kaye, "U-V" 1987, Correspondents include Javier Perez de Cuellar, Peter Ueberroth, Jack Valenti, and Gwen Verdon. (Box-folder 492/7)
  - Condolences – Death of Danny Kaye, "W" 1987, Correspondents include Anne Jackson, Señor Wences, Mary Wickes, and George F. Will. (Box-folder 492/8)
  - Condolences – Death of Danny Kaye, "X-Z" 1987, Correspondents include Eugenia Zuckerman. (Box-folder 492/9)
  - Condolences – Death of Danny Kaye, Unidentified, 1987, Fire damaged (Box-folder 791/4)
  - Condolences – Death of Danny Kaye - Letters to Dena Kaye, 1987, Fire damaged; Correspondents Helen Gurley Brown, Abraham Ribicokk, Diane Sawyer, and Benay Venuta. (Box-folder 791/5)
  - Condolences – Death of Danny Kaye - Response Lists, undated, Fire damaged (Box-folder 791/6)
  - Condolences – Death of Larry Kaye 1968 (Box-folder 492/10)
  - Coward, Noël, 1973 (Box-folder 791/7)
  - Craig, David, 1979, 1987-1988, undated (Box-folder 492/11)
  - Cranston, Alan, 1974 (Box-folder 492/12)
  - Curtiz, Michael, 1953 (Box-folder 492/13)
  - "C" Miscellaneous, 1948-1987, Correspondents include Hugh Carey, Buff Chandler, Joyce Chen, Jack Kent Cooke, and Marion Cunningham. (Box-folder 492/14)
  - De Mille, Agnes, 1980-1987 (Box-folder 492/15)
  - Deutsch, Armand S., 1974, 1987 (Box-folder 492/16)
  - Dickenson, Angie, 1985 (Box-folder 492/17)
  - Donat, Robert, 1948, 1951 (Box-folder 492/18)
  - Douglas, Kirk and Anne, 1981, 1984, undated (Box-folder 492/19)
  - Drury, Allen, 1974 (Box-folder 492/20)
  - Dutch Royal Family, 1967, 1982-1985, Correspondents include Queen Beatrix and Princess Margriet.; Includes photograph of Danny Kaye. (Box-folder 492/21)
  - "D" Miscellaneous, 1963-1984, Correspondents include Michael deBakey, Edward deBartolo, and Harry Ellis Dickson.; Includes photographs of Danny Kaye. (Box-folder 493/1)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight and Mamie, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 493/2)
  - "E" Miscellaneous, 1952-1983 (Box-folder 493/3)
  - Fabray, Nanette, 1988 (Box-folder 493/4)
  - Fairbanks, Douglas and Mary Lee, 1958, 1985, undated (Box-folder 493/5)
  - Fellini, Federico, 1968 (Box-folder 493/6)
  - Fine, Sylvia, undated (Box-folder 493/7)
  - Fonda, Jane, undated (Box-folder 493/8)
  - Fonteyn, Margot, 1957, 1985, undated (Box-folder 493/9)